Money is sizeable.
□這筆錢數目龐大 足以摧毀犯罪集團□
It will destroy the crime syndicate.
□來了
Oh, there!
□（國際機場）□
Perhaps I didn't make myself
□也許上周我在股東大會上□ 說得還不夠清楚□
cl ear enoughat the board meeting last week.
□這原本是我父親的公司□ 現在歸我管了□
It was my father's company,it is now my company.
But the money will go to Maha Jaya.
□錢一定要用在瑪哈扎雅□ 沒餘地可談□
We are done here.
Hi, Tian Xiao Xian.
□田小姐 我是大使館負責您安保的□
I'm Madame Liang,head of Embassy Security.
The ambassador has asked me to look after you.
□叫我小梁就行□
Call me Xiao Xian.
□你可以叫我小嫻□
With the increasing
□隨著中國企業在瑪哈扎雅的□ 經濟影響力日漸增加□
economic impact
of Chinese businesses in Maha Jaya,
crimes against the local Chinese community
□針對華人社區的犯罪行動逐日攀升□
have been on the rise.
The Chinese embassy has been working
□中國大使館和當地機構緊密合作□
with the local authorities
to take special measures to keep our countrymen safe.
□採取特別措施以保護國人的安全□
Now,with the alleged involvement
□據說有強大的犯罪組織參與□
of a powerful criminal organization,
□引起了更大的擔憂□
there is cause for even greater concern.
Chinese heiress, Tian Xiao Xian,
□中國公司的女繼承人田小嫻□ 剛剛到達瑪哈扎雅□
has just arrived in Maha Jaya
with a plan to take down the syndicate.
□她計劃摧毀犯罪集團□
三重威脅之跨國大營救
□VansionSubTeam 校訂翻譯
That thing won't work out here.
□那東西在這沒用的□
Those guys, they're our GPS and navigation system.
□那兩個人來幹嘛？□
□他們就是我們的定位導航系統□
That's why we brought 'em.
□所以才帶他們來□
Ah, there you are.
□總算找到你了□
Look at you, looking all dapper.
□瞧你這人模人樣的□
Time to ruin your day.
□接下來就該倒霉了□
We're in business.
□準備動手□
□（軍情六處秘密黑獄□ 瑪哈扎雅叢林）□
Don't speak, love.
□別說話 親愛的□
Don't leave me.
□別丟下我□
Hey!
□我不是說了嗎？□留意身後 集中注意力□
What did I tell you?
Watch your six. Pay attention.
□你知道我能照顧好我自己□
You know I can take care of myself.
What are you doing?
□你在幹什麼？□
Let's go.
□走吧！□
Here, grab this.
□來 把這燒了□
Do not move.
Good morning.
□早上好□
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
□你知道自己在做什麼嗎？□
Yeah, I'm pretty sure I do.
□當然 清清楚楚□
□你要付出代價的□
There's a cost here.
Think twice before you continue.
□請你三思後行□
If there's a cost,put it on my credit card.
□有代價的話 就記我信用卡上吧□
□你一定就是大老闆吧□
So, you must be the big boss.
Kinda tall to be a Burmese.
□長這麼高 不是緬甸人吧□
I'm Indonesian.
□我是印尼人□
Oh, okay, my bad, Indonesian.
□好吧 是我搞錯了 你是印尼人□
□你一定瞭解我們的作風□
And you to us?
Maybe you and I could make a deal?
□咱們是否可以做筆交易？□
Colonel, we found him at the north side of the camp.
□上校 我們在營地北邊找到他了□
Let's take ol' white collar with us.
□我們把這老白領帶上□
Pretty sure Collins hasn't had his breakfast yet.
□柯林斯肯定還沒吃上早飯呢□
Don't shoot!We're with the Americans!
□我們和軍情六處有協議的□
We had an agreement with the mercies!
Hey, where's the women and children?
□喂 女人和孩子在哪？□
Hey.
□喂！□
□別管了□
Leave that alone.
He said leave that alone.
□他叫你別管了□
So leave it alone.
□你別管了□
Get the thermite cutter.
□去拿鋁熱劑鍛刀□
You're making the biggest mistake of your life.
□你這是在犯人生最大的錯誤□
The man is a major terrorist.
□那人是主要恐怖分子□
You think my agency is just gonna let this go?
□你覺得局裡會放過你們嗎？□
You better pray he's still alive.
□你最好祈禱他還活著□
Yeah.
□天哪！□
Don't think you're gonna enjoy your freedom.
□我不覺得自由會給你快樂□
You're gonna bring a world of hurt onto yourselves.
□你會給自己帶來無盡的傷害□
I told you you'd be beggin' on your knees tonight.
□我跟你說過 你有天會跪地求饒的□
Go to hell.
□去死吧！□
You first.
□你先去□
Here you go.
□來一口□
Spa treatment is over, Collins.
□柯林斯 水療結束了□
Let's torch this place and get out of here.
□我們現在把這地方燒了 然後走人□
□不留一絲痕跡□
No evidence.
We burn this place and everyone in it.
□把這地方和所有人都燒了□
Your clothes, mate.You might need them.
□給你備了些衣服□
□想到你應該要換換□
Maybe a shower. You stink.
□可能還要洗個澡□
□你臭得要命□
Forgive me for what I have to do.
□我一定得這麼做 原諒我□
□我沒有選擇□
I have no choice.
□（中國女繼承人田小嫻捐出家產□ 助力打擊犯罪集團）□
Su Feng, Collins has been extracted.
□蘇鳳□
□柯林斯已經被救出來了□
I'm glad we could
□很慶幸我們能擱置分歧□
put aside our differences on this.
He's a loose cannon.
□他就是匹脫韁野馬□
I think it's a mistake,but it's your play.
□我覺得這是個錯誤 但這是你的遊戲□
□我們現在互不相欠□
We're square now.
□還有一件事□
One more thing.
Get me her itinerary.
□幫我把她的行程弄來□
They are in the arena.
□他們在拳擊場裡□
It better be the two men I'm looking for.
□最好是我要找的那兩個人□
Here you go.
□讓我進去□
□500□
Five. Okay? Five hundred.
□500成不成？□
Five.
Payu! We're on! Let's go!
□帕玉 我們走！□
Yeah!
□來吧！□
Let's beat him!
- Hey, come on!- Come on!
Yeah!
Hey! Huh?
□喂！□
I want in.
-I'll pay you. -Okay.
- Yeah! -Bro.
□真棒！□
Place a bet more. Place more.
Come on!
□加油！□
□記得我嗎？□
Remember me? Huh? I remember you.
□我可記得你□
You killed my wife.
□是你殺了我老婆□
For this, I will kill you.
□我會殺了你報仇□
Shit!
□媽的！□
Come on!
That's the guy from the camp.
□-他是營地裡的那個人□ □-是他□
Yeah.
Give me a hand.
□幫我一把□
How is he?
□他怎麼樣了？□
He's lost a lot of blood.
□他失了很多血□
He needs food.
□他需要吃東西□
I made one for him.
□我給他做了飯□
He was trying to kill me.
□他差點要了我命□
I would do the same.
□我要是他 我也會這麼做□
We need to talk.
□我們得談談□
I buried many of my friends because of you two.
□因為你倆幹的好事□ □我親手埋葬了很多朋友□
It's not what you think.
□事實不是你想那樣□
You were with the killers that came into my camp.
□當時你們和到我營裡的殺手在一起□
We were told we were on a humanitarian mission,
□他們告訴我們□ □是參加人道主義行動□
but we were lied to.
□但那是騙人的□
Hey! What about the prisoners?
□喂！那囚犯怎麼處置？□
Oh, yeah, yeah, um, Dom,
□啊對了 多姆□
reunite them with the prisoners.
□讓他們跟囚犯團圓吧□
This place reminds me of Boy Scout camp.
□這地方讓我想起童軍營□
-In you go.
A bunch of assholes there as well.
□那兒也有很多混蛋□
Five-minute fuse, Collins.
□柯林斯 五分鐘後引爆□
Fuck it up, Mook.
□阿木 上鎖！□
Come push me.
□推我一把□
Get out of here!
□離開這！□
□快來！□
Come, come, come.Come on. It's about to explode.
□-快點！□□-快跑！□
Go! Go!
Come on!
How long do we have?
□我們還剩多長時間？□
CL-21 explosive device.
□這是CL21爆炸裝置□
Less than one minute.
□不到一分鐘□
I can't diffuse this.
□我沒辦法拆□
□-快跑！□□-跑！□
-Go, go, go! -Go!
□所有人都出去！出去！□
Everybody out, out!
- Go! -No, you go!
□-快跑！□□-你快跑！□
We didn't fire our weapons.
□我們沒有開火□
We thought we were doing something good.
□我們以為是在做好事□
Yeah, no good there.
□對 其實跟好事根本不沾邊□
We were double-crossed and left for dead.
□我們被出賣了 他們把我們丟在那□ □讓我們等死□
We are after the same men.
□我們想找的是同一幫人□
Who are they?
□-他們是什麼人？□-某個犯罪集團□
Some kind of criminal gang.
□無惡不作的人□
Really bad guys.
What were you doing at a camp?
□你在營地是幹什麼的？□
My men and I were paid to guard the place.
□我和兄弟們受雇在那做安保□ □不過為了生存□
It was just a job.
We are soldiers for hire.
□我們是僱傭兵 所有人都會請我們□
Everyone uses us.
□那…□
So,
what's your plan?
□你們有什麼計劃？□
Make money, finance, resupply.
□賺錢、籌備資金、補上裝備□
And then, it's payback.
□-然後就開始報仇□ □-對□
-Yeah.
Not much of a plan.
□這算不上什麼計劃□
You have a better idea?
□你有更好的想法嗎？□
Perhaps, we can work together.
□也許吧 也許我們能合作□
I have a lot of contacts.I can find anyone.
□我人脈很廣 想找誰他們都找得到□
But first...
□但首先…□
a toast.
□來乾一杯□
To new friends.
□-敬新的朋友□ □-敬新的朋友□
-To new friends.-To new friends.
Yeah.
□沒錯□
One more, don't be shy.
□再來一杯□
□-別見外□ □-好！□
Yup.
Yeah.
□好！□
My father loved it here.
□我爸很喜歡這兒□
How is the ambassador?
□脹大使最近好嗎？□
He was a good friend of my father.
□-他是我爸的好朋友□ □-他很好□
He's doing well.
He speaks highly of your father.
□我聽他提起過您父親□
We'll arrive for your interview in an hour.
□我們會在一個小時內到達演播室□
I just want to say how much I admire the work
□我一直很仰慕您的慈善事業□
you've been doing here for the past week.
Thanks.I'm not sure I deserve it.
□謝謝你 客氣了□
Well, I think you do.And so do a lot of others.
□是真的 我們一直都很支持你□
Thank you.It's good to hear that.
□謝謝 有時候總覺得沒人懂□
Sometimes I feel like I'm walking alone.
What?
□怎麼了？□
□他走了□
He's gone.
I didn't hear him leave.
□我沒聽見他離開的聲音□
I guess he did not like my cooking.
□他可能不喜歡我做的菜□
-Yeah, well...-Yeah.
□是吧…□
□那也是一個原因□
There is that.
I think we've been set up.
□-我覺得我們被下套了□ □-什麼？□
What?
Freeze! Put your hands above your head. Don't move!
-Handcuffs! Bring them out!-Okay, officer.
□好了好了□
□（警察）□
Oh, man.
□我的天哪□
□（中央警察局）□
Yes?
□-喂？□□-請給柯林斯帶個話□
This is a message for Collins.
Collins?
□柯林斯？□
No one here by that name.
□我沒聽說過這個人□
Trust me,he'll wanna know.
□聽我說 他一定會想知道□
You have a message for Collins,you can talk to me.
□給柯林斯的話可以跟我說□
Tell him
□告訴他叢林突擊的兩個追蹤者□
that the two chaps from the jungle raid
are in custody at Central Police Station.
□現在被關在了中央警察局□
□（警察）□
□你每次都帶我去最棒的地方□
You take me to the nicest places.
Are you being sent back to China?
□你會被遣返回中國嗎？□
The gang took everything from us.
□幫派從我們身上奪走了一切□
I didn't want it to be this way.
□我也不想結果是這樣的□
Pa?
□爸□
I want to go home.
□我要回家□
□（那加瓦拉酒店）□
Miss Tian,we're so pleased to have you.
□田小姐 您能來我們深感榮幸□
We'd like to lead into the interview
□採訪中我們想先聊□ □有關您父親的背景□
with some background about your father,
your inheritance.
□還有您繼承的遺產 這樣可以嗎？□
Would that be all right?
Let's try to keep the personal questions
□我們盡量少聊私人問題□ □我來這主要是聊慈善事業的□
to a minimum.
I'm here for the charity.
- Okay, sure, understand. -Great.
□-好的沒問題 我明白□ □-很好□
The two guides you used in the jungle
□你們在叢林裡用的那兩個人□ □現在在中央警察局□
are down at the Central Police Station.
Central Police Station? Really?
□中央警察局？□
□真的嗎？□
Well, that is very interesting.
□這就有趣了□
I suggest you take care of this immediately.
□我建議你立刻把這事解決了□
Understood.
□明白□
Those two little jungle rats
□你請的那兩隻叢林鼠沒被炸死□
who shouldn't have survived that explosion.
That's not possible.
□那不可能 我們在籠裡放的C-4炸藥□□ 足以把附近一切生物炸死□
We piled enough composition four in those cages
to kill everything in the vicinity.
Well, two resilient inmates at Central
□中央警局裡有兩位生命力頑強的獄友□ 會證明你是錯的□
would disagree with you.
Let's stay focused in on point.
□我們先專心幹好這件事□
We'll deal with those mavericks as and when.
□必要時再處理那兩隻怪物□
Crimes against the local Chinese community.
□（瑪哈扎雅新聞）□
□針對本地華人社區的犯罪活動□ □日益增加□
Have been on the rise.
Chinese heiress, Tian Xiao Xian,
□今天在直播間跟達蒙一起的□ □是中國富商千金田小嫻□
will join Damon live in the studio today
□她會講述打擊犯罪集團的計劃□
to talk about her plans
to push back against the syndicate.
You know her as the daughter
□她是你們所知的中國地產巨頭的千金□
of Chinese real estate mogul,
Tian Wai Gow.
□田偉高□
She's the heiress who set aside her pampered life,
□這位繼承人□ □將養尊處優的生活擱在一邊□
and shared her wealth with those in need.
□選擇與需要的人分享她的財富□
Since her father's passing,she has devoted herself
□自從她父親過世以來 她就致力於□
□這座城市的慈善事業□ □預防犯罪和貪污的工作中□
and her family's fortune to philanthropy,
crime prevention,and corruption in our city.
□將家族財產投入至其中□
It's my distinct pleasure to welcome Miss Xiao Xian.
□能邀請到小嫻 我深感榮幸□
Thank you, Damon.
□謝謝你 達蒙□
You were born to wealth.
□你出身於富裕的家庭□
You've never had to work unless you decided to do so.
□除非下定決心 你並不需要工作□
So, why?
□所以為什麼呢？□
Why take such a risk in such a dangerous cause?
□為什麼要為這麼危險的事業□ □冒這麼大的險？□
My father grew up here.
□我父親是在這裡長大的□
And Maha Jaya is a very special place to him.
□他對瑪哈扎雅有著特殊的情感□
Children don't have the luxury of playing outside,
□對這裡的孩子來說□ □到室外玩耍是遙不可及的事情□
because it's simply not safe.
□因為不安全□
The investment allows us to build the infrastructure,
□這筆投資可以讓我們構建基礎建設□
so that the people of this country
□讓這個國家的人可以享受教育□
can have access to an education,
creating real jobs and, in turn, an economy.
□創造真正的工作機會 從而建設經濟□
My father told me that the greatest wealth
□我爸爸告訴我說最大的財富□
is being able to live a life of service to others.
□是過為他人服務的人生□
I want nothing more than to give these people
□我最想要的 不過是給這些人□
the same chance that I was given,
□我所擁有的機會□
so they can experience the joy of family,
□讓他們能體會家庭的快樂□
love, and a safe place to call home.
□體會愛□
□體會一個名為家的安全港灣□
These crime syndicates must go.
□這些犯罪集團必須消失□
The people, the children,are the future of this country.
□民眾和孩子是國家的未來□
□見到他們時 我看到的是…□
When I see them,I see...
resilience, hope, and strength.
□堅韌□
□希望 還有力量□
□據可靠消息稱□
We look forward to that.
□你捐出的是一筆巨款□
The donation you're making is very sizeable.
It is not a donation. It is an investment in humanity.
□這不算是捐款□ □而是在人道事業上的投資□
The money allows them
□這筆錢能讓他們有所選擇□
to have options,
so that they can get on the right side of the law.
□這樣他們就能選擇依法行事□
So that crime syndicates don't have a grip
□讓犯罪集團無法利用人們的恐懼□ □來控制他們□
on these people through fear.
□（採訪五分鐘後結束）□
All right,she's leaving the hotel.
□好的 她即將出酒店□
Ten-four.
□收到□
Moving forward.
□往前開□
What kind of security are we talking?
□我們面對的是什麼安保程度？□
Rent-a-cops.
□業餘保安 我們一攪亂場子□ □他們就會散開□
They'll scatter as soon as we turn up the heat.
We are in business.
□行動開始□
Let's do it.
□開干吧□
Thank you, Xiao Xian.
□謝謝你 小嫻□
It has been an honor to speak with you today.
□今天能跟你聊天 我深感榮幸□
Thank you so much.
□非常謝謝你□
Go! Go! Move! Move!
□快去！動起來！□
-Hide behind me.
□躲到我身後！□
-Don't mind me.
□不要管我！□
Run to the police station.
□你跑向警察局 讓他們聯繫大使館□
They'll get you to the embassy.
What about you?
□你怎麼辦？□
Don't mind me. Three, two, one.
□不要管我！一、二、三！□
Joey, get in the van.
□喬伊你開車走□ □德弗羅和阿木去市場□
move to market.
Dom, you go south.
□多姆往南走 斯坦納跟我走□ □現在出發！□
Steiner, you're with me, now!
Can you please help me? Please! Please!
□能幫幫我嗎！求你了！去警察局？□
Police station! Please!
- Take me to the police station!- Okay.
□-請帶我去警察局□ □-好□
Right away!
Stop!
□-別動！□□-別動！□
- What are you doing? -Stop!
-...son of a bitch!
Come on! Get in!Let's go!
□來啊 上車！我們走！□
□安全了！□
Dominique's dead.He was out of control.
□多姆死了 他失控了□
She's gone.Fucked off in a tuk-tuk.
□她跑了 坐上了該死的嘟嘟車逃了□
The intel was wrong.You almost got us killed.
□你的情報有誤 害我們差點喪命□
Deal with it, Devereaux.
□面對現實吧 德弗羅□
We get paid to almost get killed.
□我們的工作就是走在死亡邊緣□ □關鍵詞是「邊緣「□
Key word. "Almost."
Quit your moanin'.
□別埋怨了□
There's another loose end
□還有一個未了結的問題要處理□
we need to deal with.
Who's more important than killing the girl?
□有什麼比殺了那女的更重要？□
Your two zombie trackers back from the dead, that's who.
□是你請的那兩個殭屍追蹤者□ □起死回生了□
They can ID every single one of us.
□他們可以認出我們每一個人□ □要封住他們的口□
They need to be silenced.
You wanna hit the police station?
□-是要突襲警察局嗎？□□-對就是警察局□
Yes, a police station,
not a castle with a fuckin' moat.
□而非帶護城河的城堡□
Those cops are on cruise control.
□警察現在都在做夢呢□ □肯定想不到我們會出現□
They won't be expecting us.
I'm surprised if they're even awake.
□他們要醒著 我會很吃驚□
□（中央警察局）□
Please! Help me! Please!
□救命！□
□救命啊！□
Please! Help me! Please!
□拜託救救我！□
They've been trying to kill me.
□他們試圖謀殺我！□
I...
□我當時置身槍戰之中 你懂嗎？□
I was just in a shootout.
Do you understand?
Do you...
□你會…□
Do you speak English? Chinese?
□你會說英文嗎？中文？□
Look at this! That's me!
□看到了嗎？那是我□
See? That's me.
-Yes. That's me.-She's on TV.
□-就是我□ □-電視上那女的？□
Come in! Here.
Sit down!
□坐下！□
Take it easy, officer.
□放輕鬆 長官□
You are involved
□你參與了非法鬥毆和賭博□
in illegal fighting and gambling.
Are you asking me or telling me?
□你是在問我問題 還是告訴我事實？□
Don't lock it up yet.
Move.
Chinese?
□是中國人嗎？□
I would say we have five
□我覺得我們最多有五到十分鐘□
to ten minutes max.
Go in and out quick,shock and awe, baby.
□我們速戰速決 以勢震敵□
Devereaux, you're on the wheel.Joey, you're with us.
□德弗羅你留車上 喬伊跟我們走□ □出發！□
Let's go.
□我們走□
Hey, you're the one on TV?
□你不是電視上那個誰嗎？□
You're Chinese? Great!
□中國人？太好了！□
Ask her what happened at the hotel.
Tell him someone is trying to kill me.
□你幫我跟他說我被人追殺了□
You think you're better than us?
□你以為我們所有人都比不過你□ □就因為你當過兵？□
Because you are an ex-soldier?
□在我看來 你不過是只小貓□
You're nothing but a pussy to me.
□這樣如何？□
□你不開口的話 就坐一輩子牢！□
How about this?
If you don't talk,you go to prison!
Stay low and away from the windows!
Let's move.
See what's happening.
Go, quickly!
We have to bring chief out of here.
Guard him!
□看好他！別讓他跑了！□
-Don't let him go anywhere!-Yes, sir!
They're coming!
□他們追來了！□
Can you get me out of here?
□你能帶我出去嗎？□
I don't know how.
□我自己都不知道能不能出去□
□長官 請放我走！□
Officer, please let me go!
- Let's sort this out, officer.
Stop!
□站住！□
Long-Fei!
□龍飛！□
Stay here!
□留在這！□
Shit.
□糟糕！□
We need to find another way out.
□我們要另尋出口□
Get up! On your feet!
□起來 站好了！□
Where do they keep
the prisoners?
□他們把囚犯關哪？□
Where are the prisoners?
They aren't here!
All prisoners are locked up downstairs.
Prisoners are downstairs in holding.
□囚犯在樓下關著□
Mook!Break out the door!
□阿木 把門轟開！□
Check every single hallway.
□檢查每一條走道□□阿木 你上來和我一起□
Mook, I need you upstairs with me.
I'm on my way, Collins.
□我在路上了 柯林斯□
Just who I was looking for.
□正是我要找的人□
The girl had nothing to do with this.
□不關這姑娘的事□
She's everything to do with this.
□她就是罪魁禍首□
What?
□什麼？□
What are you talking about?
□-你說什麼呢？□□-今天我真走運□
This is my lucky day.
Get out of here!
□快跑！□
- Huh?
You. You set this up.
□這全是你設的局□
I did it to flush them out.
□我只是想引蛇出洞□
You should go.
□你該走了 和你朋友一起□
Leave with your friend.
Go.
Move! Quickly!
Don't do it.
□別這麼做□
Well, well, well.
□太巧了吧□
□真是太驚喜了□
What a nice surprise.
Joey!
□喬伊！□
Go!
□走！□
Take the girl!
□帶這姑娘離開這裡！□
Get out of here!
Go!
□走！□
- Gotta go now! Go!
□我們得快跑了！□
Come on!
□快跑！□
Come on.
□來啊！□
Go!
□走！□
Shit.
□媽的□
Everybody fall back.
□全體撤退□
Big man, meet me at the south side alley way.
□大塊頭 到南邊小巷等我□
- Huh?
Get in!
□-上車！□□-快走！□
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
- Move it!-All right!
□快跑！□
□知道了！□
□快點！別停下來！□
Oh! Please!
Keep moving. Keep moving.Go! Keep moving.
□快跑！□
I said the south side.Where are ya?
Go!
□開車！□
Mook! Where's Mook?
□阿木！阿木呢？□
- She's fuckin' dead, all right?- Shit.
□-她死了行了嗎？□□-靠□
- And Steiner? -Steiner, too.
□-斯坦納呢？□-也死了□
This is turning into a real shit show.
□這成他媽的電影了是嗎？□
This is an expensive fuckin' exercise.
□代價慘重的狗屁任務□
Who are these fuckin' bush babies you hired anyway?
□你雇的到底是什麼破猴？□
Just local trackers from one of the villages.
□就是當地村裡的追蹤者□
From like a village of fuckin' ninja warrior land?
□是那狗屁忍者戰地裡的村？□
Jesus Christ!
□我的天！□
They have to be down one of these streets.
□他們一定在附近一條街上□
-There they are!
□就在那！□
Guys.
□注意了□
Moving! Moving! Move!
□快跑！□
- Huh?- Wait, what?
□等等 怎麼回事？□
Come on!
There they fucking are!
□那些人在那！□
In here! Move!
Get out of the way!
□讓開！□
Fuckin' move!
□滾開！□
Down here!
□這邊！□
-Whoa!
- Fuckin' hell! Jesus!
□他媽的！老天哪！□
- Whoa!
Shut the fuck up! Fuck off!
□往後退！□
They're gone!
□他們逃了！□
Fuck!
□操！□
Now you get the van,get to Devereaux.
□-你去車上 去找德弗羅□ □-不！□
No way.
□-我們在集市那碰頭□ □-我跟你走□
You meet me at the marketplace there.
No, you do as your fuckin' told and get in the van.
□-聽我指令 去車上□ □-你以為是在跟誰說話？□
Who do you think you're talking to, eh?
You keep telling me what to do,and you're pissing me off.
□你不停給我命令 真惹毛我了□
We're running around the streets with fuckin' machine guns.
□我們拿著他媽的機關鎗在街上亂跑□
□看多少人盯著我們□ □警察很快就會來了吧？□
Look at the eyes on us!
How long is it gonna be before the police turn up?
□拿著 去車上 乖乖服從指令□
You take that,you get to the van,
and you do as you're fucking told!
□大使□
Sir.
Oh. Lee,you've arrived just in time.
□小李 你來得正好 你□
These are signed.
□這份文件我已經簽過字了□
You can send them out.
□可以上報了□
Of course, but I have something urgent to report.
□好 我知道了□
□張大使 有件事情要向您匯報□
What?
□什麼事情？□
There has been an attack on the Nagavara Hotel.
□就在剛才 一群不明身份的歹徒□ □持槍襲擊了那加瓦拉酒店□
Are Liang and Xiao Xian safe?
□現在小嫻和小梁情況怎麼樣？□
Liang is injured.She's in the hospital.
□小梁受傷了 已送往醫院□
Xiao Xian is missing.
□但是田小嫻她失蹤了□
Missing?
□失蹤了？□
Liang believes Xiao Xian must have run
□我想田小嫻現在應該正在跑向□ □我們中國大使館□
to the Chinese Embassy.
But so far,we haven't heard from her.
□但是到目前為止我們還沒有接到□ □任何關於她的消息□
Get me the Maha Jaya Chief of Police.
□給我接瑪哈扎雅警察總長的電話□
Yeah?
□對□
You messed up the contract, Collins.
□你把合同搞得一團糟 柯林斯□
Do I need to engage someone else to take care of this?
□我需要讓別人插手嗎？□
Whoa, whoa, whoa.Slow down, Su Feng.
□天哪 慢著蘇鳳□
Everything's under control,all right?
□-所有事情都在掌控之中 行嗎？□□-如果這都算掌控之中□
If this is under control,
I'd hate to see what out of control looks like.
□我可沒眼看失控是什麼樣子□
It'll look like me decimating any other team
□會是我將礙我事的小組趕盡殺絕□ □所以別插手□
that gets in my way,
so back off and let us do our job.
□讓我們完成工作□
You should come and see me.
□你該來見見我□
Not yet.
□還不行 我會在明天前通通搞定□
I'll have this spotless before the sun comes up.
I'll come and see you then.
□我到時再來見你□
Freeze!
Put your hands up!
I haven't got time for this.
□我沒空理你□
Turn back! Put your hands on your head!
You're makin' a big mistake, pal.
□兄弟 你這是犯了大錯□
We're after the same people.
□我們在找同一幫人□
We should talk.
□-我們該談談□ □-朋友 我現在有點忙□
I'm a little busy right now, mate.
Drop the gun.
□把槍放下□
□站起來□
Stand up.
What do you want?
□你想要什麼？□
Let's not play games.
□我們別繞彎子了□
I could work with you.
□我可以跟你合作□
I can help you take down the dude that you're after.
□我幫你拿下你要找的那兩人□
I'm not looking for an apprentice right now.
□我沒想找一個徒弟 謝謝你□
Thank you very much.
Who exactly are they,and what do you want with them?
□他們到底是誰？你找他們幹什麼？□
They're mercenaries,like me.
□他們是僱傭兵□
□和我一樣□
I've been after them for years.
□我找他們好幾年了□
Looking at your situation,I'd say you need some help.
□看你這情況 我覺得你需要幫忙□
And how exactly do you suppose you're gonna help me?
□你覺得你可以怎麼幫我？□
I know my way around the city.
□我在城裡人脈很廣□
And I know the same people they do and how they work.
□他們認識的人我都認識□ □也知道他們如何行動□
Long-Fei and Payu,
□龍飛和帕玉□
they also have the girl you're after.
□你要找的女孩也在他們手上□
Look, if we work together, we can both get what we want.
□聽著 如果我們聯手□ □我們可以得到各自想要的□
You can certainly handle yourself.
□你完全可以自己搞定□
Maybe I could use a little bit of local assistance.
□也許我可以利用當地人的幫助□
We better get out of here
□我們最好在他同伴來到之前走人□ □不是嗎？□
before his mates turn up don't you?
Yeah.
□對□
What were you doing
□你們是怎麼進警察局的？□
at the police station?
We were in an underground fight.
□我也不知道怎麼就進去了□
There may have been some gambling involved.
□我們不過打了一場地下拳賽而已□
Did you guys win?
□贏了嗎？□
Of course. We are professionals.
□當然□
□我們是專業的□
And he is?
□他是？□
That's Payu.
□他是帕玉□
Payu, thank you for saving me.
□帕玉？□
□謝謝你救了我□
Thank you.
Anytime.
Can I trust you guys?
□我能相信你們嗎？□
The police aren't an option.Do you have a choice?
□警察局是不能去了□ □你還有別的選擇嗎？□
I grew up near here.
□我在這附近長大□
□(理髮店)□
Go, go, go.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Get down.
□蹲下□
What are you doing?
□-你在幹嘛？□□-你開車 我給你指路□
You drive. I'll navigate.
You realize this is a cop car, right?
□-你知道這是警察的車嗎？□□-我們只是借用一下而已□
We're just going to borrow it.
You should drive.
□-還是你開吧□ □-這是女孩開的車□
This is a girl's car.
Since when do cars have genders? This is not the time to joke.
□開車有分男女的嗎？□□這不是開玩笑的時候□
I'm not joking. I can't drive.
□我沒開玩笑 我不開車□
What do you mean you can't drive?
□不開車是什麼意思？□
I mean, I don't know how to drive.
□意思就是 我不會開車□
You're a professional? How come you can't drive?
□你不是專業的嗎？怎麼不會開車呢？□
I'm a professional, just not a professional driver.
□專業的？我又不是專業開車的□
Shit.
□我靠□
Here.
□來□
Hey, my car!
Hey, stop!
Where are you going?
Look,
□聽著 我們會把工作完成的 行嗎？□
we'll get the job done,all right?
Trust me.
□相信我□
It'll be business as usual before...
□一切都照常進行 直到你…喂？□
- Hello?
So, what's up?
□所以怎麼樣了？□
Ah, that Su Feng meeting didn't go well.
□和蘇鳳的會議進行得不怎麼順利□
She's even more pissed off than she normally is.
□她比平常火氣更大了□
You said you could handle it.
□你說你能搞定的□
Yeah.
□是□
So, what does that mean?
□那是什麼意思？□
Well, it's pretty simple,really.
□其實真的很簡單□
We've got 48 hours to execute those little pricks
□我們有48小時幹掉那幾個混蛋□ □否則…□
and if we don't,
□合同就反過頭衝我們來了□
contract reverts to us.
Nah, not alcohol.
□不 我不喝酒□
Jesus.
□老天哪□
Remind me and the lads why we need you again.
□再給我和兄弟們說說…□
□我們要你幹嘛？□
All of you are ex-military.
□你們全是當過兵的□
Maybe special forces?
□是在特種部隊待過嗎？□
Martial arts training.
□受過武術訓練□
But maybe a bit out of shape.
□但身材似乎有點走樣□
You don't know us well enough to be making
□你有多瞭解我們 有資格說這話嗎？□
that kind of statement now,do you?
You were saying?
□你剛說什麼？□
All right, calm down.
□好了 冷靜些□
Devereaux.
□德弗羅□
He's useful.
□他還有用□
Crew is light anyways,so I say we keep him.
□隊裡沒剩幾個人了 把他留著吧□
Like I said, if you're going after Long-Fei and Payu,
□就像我說的…□
□如果想找到龍飛和帕玉的話□
you need my help.
□你們會需要我幫助的□
This little motherfucker just doesn't quit, does he?
□這小混蛋毫不放棄 不是嗎？□
Look, we've got contacts coming out of our asses, mate.
□聽著兄弟 我們到處布著線人□
Pretty soon, someone somewhere is gonna give her up.
□很快就會有人把她供出來□
She is well-connected in China and has nowhere to go.
□她的人脈都在中國□
□也沒別的地方去了□
She will head to the Chinese Embassy.
□她一定會去中國大使館□
□（中國大使館）□
I thought Maha Jaya
□靠 不是說瑪哈扎雅不堵車的嗎？□
fixed their traffic problem.
Something is wrong.
□有點不對勁□
This can't be a coincidence.
□這不可能是巧合□
It has to be them.
□他們一定在那□
□能借你電話用用嗎？□
Can I borrow your phone?
Okay.
□好□
Xiao Xian, where are you?
□小嫻 你在哪？□
Madame Liang,I hope you're better now.
□小梁 你沒事吧？□
We can see the embassy,
□我們現在已經看見大使館了□ □可是被堵住了□
but we're stuck behind the roadblock.
There was a bomb threat at the embassy.
□你先別過來□
□剛剛有人威脅要炸大使館□
We think it was them.
□很難說是不是同一夥人幹的□
It's all blocked.
□全部封鎖了□
Who are you with?
□你跟誰在一起？□
Some new friends.They're helping me out.
□我新認識的朋友 他們在幫我□
I'm moving now.
□我現在過去□
Go, go, go!
Go. Drive.
□走 開車！□
Drive!
□開車！□
Faster. Go, go!
□快走！□
- Come on!
Get back to the van and cut 'em off.
□-我們要回車上 攔住他們□ □-對！□
Yeah, yeah.
Hey!
Are you okay?
□你沒事吧？□
Who is he?
□你怎麼認識他們的？□
Not a friend.
□不算認識□
We have to go. Now!
□我們得現在就走！□
Let me see.
Huh?
To the center, do you copy?
No one's here.
Jaka.
□扎卡□
They're in the other market.
□他們在另一個市場□
Between Kwang and Kent.
□就在光街和肯特街之間□
- Jaka.- What are you doing?
□-扎卡□ □-你在幹嘛？□
You used us a bait.
□你用我們作誘餌□
Be patient, my friend.
□耐心等等 朋友□
My fight is with Collins,not you.
□我是在跟柯林斯斗 不是你們□
Just keep moving.
□繼續走 別停□
It's your funeral, man.
□你等死吧□
This way!
□這邊！□
They were here.We just lost them.
□他們剛剛在這 又讓他們給跑了□
And here you are.
□你也在這□
I followed them from the crash.Lost them in the market.
□他們撞車後我跟他們跑到這裡□ □在市場跟丟了□
You're always in the right placeat the right time, huh?
□你總在正確時間出現在正確地點□ □不是嗎？□
That's why you need me.
□-所以你們才需要我□ □-柯林斯□
Collins, over here.
□-在這邊□ □-幹得好□
Good job.
You know my gut has kept me alive,
□你知道我的直覺…□
□讓我活到了現在□
sort of like a sixth sense.
□有點像第六感□ □你猜我現在的直覺是什麼？□
And you know what my gut is telling me?
You're up to something.
□你心裡打著算盤□
If you have a point to make,make it.
□如果你有什麼重點要說□
□就直說好了□
Oh, I will, when the time comes.
□時候到了我會說的□
Wait. Stop.
□等等 先停下□
You go that way.I'll sweep 'em towards ya.
□你走那邊□
□我把他們往你的方向逼去□
Hold on, mate.
□等等 老兄□
Sorry, not open.
□-對不起 沒開門□ □-我是衛生部的□
Health department.
I'm the vice terminator.
□我是老鼠終結者□
Looks like you passed the inspection.
□你似乎通過檢查了□
The Maha Jaya Police Department
□瑪哈扎雅警察局自顧不暇□
is overwhelmed.
They can't guarantee Xiao Xian's safety.
□剛才警察跟我說□
□他們不能保證田小嫻的安全□
The search will have to wait
□只有等到明天 外地的支援警察到了□
until additional supportarrives tomorrow.
□搜尋工作才能全面地展開□
Can I see it?
Yeah.
Looks like we're stuck here for the night.
□看來我們今晚沒有別的地方能去了□
□（我們無法干預本地執法□ □你得到領區來才能幫你 -小梁）□
Great.
□很好□
Tell me how you know these people?
□你現在可以告訴我□ □你到底是怎麼認識那幫人的嗎？□
We were hired
□本來我們是被僱用去救人的□
for a humanitarian rescue mission, only it wasn't.
Instead, they freed Collins and left us for dead.
□結果我們倆就被扔在那等死□
And who is the guy at the market?
□那小超市那個男的是誰？□
He's with the foreigners, but he's one of us.
□他雖然跟英國人在一起□ □但他是我們一夥的□
It's complicated.
□很複雜□
Complicated?
□複雜？□
His people were killed
□之前的營救行動害死了他的家人…□
when the camp was destroyed.
□所以他要找那一撥人報仇□
So, he's a mole?
□他是臥底？□
Sort of.
□算是吧□
So the two of you are responsible for this?
□原來都是你們倆做的好事□
Now, what?
□你說現在怎麼辦呢？□
Now, we take cover here for the night.
□現在…□
□今天我們只能在這過夜了□
Tomorrow, we can try the embassy again.
□明天我們一早可以去大使館試試□
Sit.
□坐□
I guess you can only call in so many bomb threats.
□好吧 他們不能每天都□□威脅炸大使館吧□
May I take your orders?
□你們要點什麼菜呢？□
Hi all. I'm Payu, your chef.
Today, I proudly present to you my best dish,
stir-fried swamp cabbage!
It's best served with hot soup,which we're gonna have...
Oops... River prawn spicy soup!
Payu was a field cook.
□帕玉以前在野戰區做炊事員□ □做飯特別好吃□
A damn good one.
You like spicy? Ooh.
□你喜歡吃辣嗎？□
Let's keep lookin'.
□繼續找□
So was it your dad's mission or yours?
□所以這是你爸的意願還是你的意願？□
It was my dad's mission that I embraced.
□是我爸的意願 也是我自己的意願□
Enough about me. What about you?
□你看 光顧著說我了 你們呢？□
You two were obviously professionally trained.
□你們受過專業訓練□
□這麼厲害□
Why did you leave China?
□為什麼你要離開祖國？□
When I was young, my father brought me here.
□小時候 我爸帶我過來□
We've been living here since then.
□我們一直在這裡生活□ □來瑪哈扎雅做私人安保能掙得多一點□
There's money working security here.
One job, two jobs.
□一單、兩單□
I want to make enough money
□很想掙夠了錢 就帶父親回國養老□
to bring my father back to China.
□可是現在就回不去了□
But now, I cannot go home.
Since you saved me, maybe I can help you?
□你救了我 這件事就交給我吧□
I know a lot of people.I'll find a way.
□我認識很多人 肯定有辦法□ □相信我好嗎？□
Ladies and gentlemen, dinner is served.
□小姐、先生□
□給你們上晚餐了□
□謝謝□
Thank you.
For me.
□用餐愉快！□
Enjoy.
This is actually really delicious.
□這真的很好吃□
You pick up a lot, moving from place to place.
□你在不同地方輾轉□ □味蕾已經很多元了□
Delicious.
□-好吃□ □-好吃□
It's good.
□好吃□
If it's good, then eat more.
□好吃就吃多點□
That's my beer.The other one's yours.
□這是我的酒 那杯才是你的□
Of course, you do. All right.
□好吧 乾杯？□
Toast?
□-乾杯□ □-乾杯□
-Cheers.-Cheers?
- Mm-hm.- Yeah, cheers.
□乾杯□
We're gonna have every syndicate hit squad
□暗殺犯罪集團小組會遍佈□ □這和中國土地一樣的印尼了□
in bloody Indochina on our cases
□除非我們快點抓到那三個小屁孩□
if we don't snare these three little imps sometime soon.
I am painfully aware of that.
□我痛苦地意識到了□
It's gonna get a lot more painful
□如果我們不解決問題會更痛苦□
if we don't solve this problem... quickly.
□要盡快解決□
Dummy. I'm always here.
□傻瓜 我一直都在□
I should never have brought you.
□我一開始就不應該帶你來這裡□
I just wanted you with me.
□我只想你在身邊□
I promise that when everything is over
□我發誓等一切結束 等他們死了…□
and they are dead,
I will live my life and make you proud.
□我會好好生活…□
I will convince them to trust me.
□讓你驕傲□
I will kill them with my bare hands.
□我會努力讓他們信任我□
On my...
□我會親手殺了他們…□
terms...
□按照我的規矩…□
at the right time.
□在正確的時間□
I will face them one by one.
□我會與他們一一單挑□
Going to the Embassy
□去大使館是個錯誤□
is a mistake.
The cartel will do anything to stop my donation.
□犯罪集團為了阻止我捐款□ □什麼都做得出來□
That's all that matters to me.
□現在最重要的就是這筆捐款□
I'm the one they're looking for.
□他們找的是我□
So give me up.
□把我供出去吧□
I don't think so.
□我覺得不行□
Use me as bait.
□用我作誘餌□
It's too dangerous.
□太危險了□
Well, we need to come up with some sort of plan.
□我們得制訂一個計劃□
You know this is the only way it could work.
□你們知道這是唯一可行的辦法□
She's right.
□她說得對□
I have an idea.
□我有個想法□
- Ah, cheers, mate.
□乾杯吧 兄弟□
Bullshit. Bullshit.Donnie and Sam, okay, cool.
□垃圾 都是垃圾□
□甄子丹和洪金寶 就它了□
Ha-ha.If it isn't the man of the hour.
□打來得真是時候□
Let me speak to Collins.
□我想和柯林斯談談□
Well, I'm pretty sure
□我肯定他也很想跟你談談□
he'd like to speak with you, too.
Hey, Collins, this is precious.
□柯林斯 有重要來電□
You're gonna wanna see this.
□你肯定想知道這好事□
Well, hello, hello, hello, mate.How's it goin'?
□喂 朋友 你還好嗎？□
How's your feet? They hurtin'?Yeah, I fuckin' hope so.
□你的腳怎麼樣？疼嗎？□□我希望疼死你□
I have something you want.Let's talk.
□我有你想要的東西 我們談談□
We're talkin' now, champ.
□我們不正談著嗎 哥們？□
We have Xian. You want her?
□小嫻在我們手上 你想要嗎？□
Oh, well, fuck me,I was not expecting that.
□我靠 真出乎我意料□
- It's bullshit, bro.- Wait, wait.
□-這是瞎扯 哥們□ □-等等 看看他說什麼□
Let's see what he's gotta say.
□我的朋友 你想怎麼樣？□
What you got in mind,my little friend?
Dawn,at the old Polo club.
□日出時 在舊時的馬球俱樂部□
You get what you want, I get $100,000 and our freedom.
□我給你那姑娘 你給我十萬美金□
□還有自由□
A hundred thousand dollars, eh?
□十萬美金？□
Yeah, all right.
□成交 幫我個忙 別遲到□
Got yourself a deal.
But do me favor, don't be late.
- I've got a deadline to meet.
□我要趕著交差□
Now you know he's trying to set us up, right?
□你很清楚他設了個陷阱吧？□
Don't tell me you trust that little bastard.
□別告訴我你相信那個王八蛋□
No, I don't trust him.
□不 我當然不信他□
But I do trust that they'll be there
□但我信不管是不是陷阱□ □他們都會到那□
whether they're settin' us up or not.
So I say we use all the cash we got left.
□按我說 我們用所有剩餘的現金□
You find me as many shooters as you can wrangle.
□你去召集所有能找到的槍手□
□-槍手？□□-對 有槍的為錢殺人的醜八怪□
- Shooters?- Yeah.
Ugly motherfuckers with guns who get paid to kill people.
- I know what shooters are. - Well, good.
□-我知道槍手是什麼□ □-那很好□
We get there early.We don't fuck about.
□我們早點去□
□不拖泥帶水 設幾個陷阱□
We set a few little traps.
And instead of negotiating the trade,
□我們不是去做交易的□
we fuckin' annihilate these little pricks,
□而是去殲滅這些王八蛋的□ □聽起來靠譜嗎？□
now how's that for trust?
Well, it's about time,
□是時候開動了□
'cause I'm sick of playin' fuckin' hide-and-seek.
□玩這狗屁捉迷藏了 我已經玩膩了□
Welcome back, Payu.
□帕玉 歡迎回來□
Let's talk inside.
□我們進裡面說□
Why are you here, Payu?
□帕玉 你為什麼來這裡？□
You callin' in your marker?
□是來索要回報的嗎？□
What makes you think I would honor it?
□你覺得我會兌現嗎？□
You are many things,
□你有很多面□
but...
□但是…□
I know you keep you word.
□我知道你是個恪守承諾的人□
You haven't told your friends about our past, have you?
□你朋友還不知道我們以前的事吧？□
How you earned your name.
□你是怎麼建立的名聲□
Payu, the tempest.
□號稱風暴帕玉□
One that destroys all that it touches.
□所及之處必然毀滅□
Not everything I did was good.
□我做的不儘是好事□
He worked with me.
□他曾與我共事□
Killed 12 men in one attack.
□在一次襲擊中殺了12個人□
I can't say they didn't deserve it.
□雖然他們都該死□
- Then he left. - No, no, no.
□-然後他就走了□ □-不是□
- Next thing you know,- Stop.
□-後來…□ □-別說了□
He's a soldier of fortune working far and wide.
□-他就成了僱傭兵 到處為…□ □-夠了！□
Enough!
You owe me.
□是你欠我的□
What do you want, Payu?
□你想要什麼 帕玉？□
I need weapons.
□我需要武器□
□你想要的都拿走□
Take what you want.
We're square.
□我們兩清了□
Your donation's not gonna change anything.
□你的捐款什麼都改變不了□
You remove one regime and another takes its place.
□打倒了一個帝國 會有另一個爬上來□
You need to stay alive to make a difference.
□你需要好好活著 才能帶來改變□
Do you have anything more substantial?
□你有更有意義的事說嗎？□
Get in. Okay.
Payu!
□帕玉！□
Don't forget what I said.We're even.
□別忘了我說的話□
□我們兩清了□
So, we're gonna take care of these little shits
□那…□
□我們搞定這些人渣□
and get back to business.
□-然後開始幹正事□ □-我們現在幹的就是正事□
This is business right now.
Split into pairs.Get into position.
□兩兩一組 各自就位 掩護主要區域□
Cover the main area. All right?
□懂了嗎？□
Go!
□去吧！□
This ends tonight.
□今晚把這事了結了□
Ah, used one of those before,haven't you?
□你用過這東西吧 對嗎？□
You know, you look like somebody who, uh, knows their guns.
□知道嗎 你看起來像是個會用槍的人□
Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
□喂□
Hey, what are you anyway, man?
□哥們 你到底是什麼人？□
□柬埔寨人？越南人？□
- Cambodian? Vietnamese?
Indonesia.
□印尼人□
Indonesian!
□印尼人！□
Yeah, yeah, man.
□太棒了 兄弟□
We ran into some Indonesians.
□我們之前碰到過印尼人□
Up in the north.
□就在北邊□
Yeah, they were being used as camp security.
□他們被僱用做營地安保□
Yeah, yeah. They were terrible.
□想起來了 他們很慘□
We deep sixed 'em all.
□我們把他們全幹掉了□
Left 'em in the sun to bloat
□把他們扔在烈日下□ □讓屍體脹大喂蒼蠅□
and feed the flies.
That doesn't bother you, does it?
□你聽著不難受吧？□
Wouldn't be anyone you knew, right?
□他們中有你認識的嗎？□
C'mon, speak up.
□你倒是說話呀□
We all on the same team. Huh?
□我們可是隊友呢□
Get off my back.
□少跟我囉嗦□
I'll get off your back.
□我不跟你囉嗦了□
I just thought it was something that you wanted
□我倒覺得是你有話想一吐為快□
to get off your little chest.
Your shooters clear
□德弗羅 那些槍手明白要求了嗎？□
on what we expect from them, Devereaux?
Yeah, I got eight guns pointed at me right now.
□對 現在有八支槍對著我呢□
□很好□
All right, good.
Let's get this done.
□我們把這事搞定□
Where's the other mouseketeer?
□另一隻老鼠去哪了？□
He's outside,making sure we weren't followed.
□他在外面 確保沒人跟蹤我們□
Is he?
□是嗎？□
Well, that's all right.We had the same idea, didn't we?
□沒問題 我們也是這麼想的 不是嗎？□
Your team double-crossed us.
□你的團隊出賣了我們□
Left us for dead.
□把我們丟在那等死□
They did.
□的確□
□但那都過去了□
But that was then, this is now.
□我們講的是現在□
So are we gonna do this or what?
□我們到底交不交換？□
There's your money in that case...
□箱子裡是你們要的錢□
just like we agreed.
□和我們說好的一樣□
Why don't you come over here,darlin'?
□親愛的 你過來如何？□
Don't worry.
□別擔心 我會讓你死得快一點的□
Promise I'll make it quick.
Do you remember the first time
□你還記得你第一次昧著良心做事□ □是什麼時候嗎？□
you felt your soul slipping away?
My soul?
□我的良心？□
No, there's no souls here,sweetheart.
□寶貝 這裡沒有良心□
Just a bunch of blokes
□我們和所有人一樣 都是在工作□
doin' our jobs like everyone else.
Now granted,
□但當然□
wasn't exactly what I wanted to be doing
□我小時候的理想並非是做這事□
when I was all grown up,
but you know what?
□但你知道嗎？□
Turned out I was pretty bloody good at it.
□結果我發現□ □我太他媽的擅長這茬了□
There's you money,just like I agreed.
□那是你要的錢□
□和說好的一樣□
The girl, send her over.
□讓那姑娘過來□
The girl! Now!
□那姑娘 馬上□
Aim the gun, pull the trigger,
□如果有人來 拔槍、射擊□ □打光所有子彈□
until it's empty.
Got it.
□知道了□
- Shit.
The Indonesians you killed were my people.
□你殺的那些印尼人…□
□都是我的弟兄□
I buried my wife because of you.
□因為你 我親手埋葬了我老婆□
This is personal.
□這是私人恩怨□
That's the dumbest thing
□那真是愚蠢至極□ □只惜你命不夠長 沒時間後悔□
you're never gonna live to regret.
Let's see.
□我們等著瞧□
Come on, you rat boss!
□來啊！你這只臭老鼠！□
Oh, I'm gonna enjoy this.
□這架打得一定大快人心□
Come on!Let's see what you got.
□來呀！□
□看看你有什麼能耐□
□你算是小個子中功夫不錯的□
Not bad for a little man.
Does it have to be this way?
□我們不一定要走到這步□
I'm afraid it does.
□恐怕一定得這樣了□
We finish this right fuckin' here!
□我們就在這鬥個你死我活□
You'll be seeing your wife soon. Shh.
□你很快就可以見到你老婆了□
Hello?
□喂？你好□
Who is this?
□你是哪位？□
Tian Xiao Xian
□田小嫻在東邊廢棄的馬球俱樂部□
is at the abandoned Polo club.
Send somebody to rescue her.
□你快派人過來救她□
- Hello?
□喂？□
Hello? Hello?
You know,you're a pretty good fighter.
□知道嗎？你的功夫還挺厲害的□
I'm gonna teach you a lesson.
□讓我來給你上一課□
Talk, talk, talk.
□廢話真多□
Now look at you.You're weak and pathetic.
□看看你 你又弱又可悲□
You sneaky, little bastard!
□你這個狡猾的小混蛋！□
I should've listened to Devereaux, shouldn't I?
□我早該聽德弗羅的話 不是嗎？□
He's dead, as you will be soon.
□他已經死了□
□你很快也會死□
Well, I reckon I fancy these odds anyway.
□我倒覺得我的勝算比較大□
Come on there, village boy.
□來呀 鄉村小子□
Jaka? Jaka!
□扎卡？扎卡□
You pissed off
□姑娘 你惹惱了一些大人物□
some really important people, girl.
For that, you have my respect.
□為此…□
□我向你致敬□
Uh-uh.
Drop it.
□放下□
Slide it over.
□把槍滑過來□
Slide it over!
It's about time I cash my paycheck,
□我該去兌現我的支票了 你覺得呢？□
don't you think?
Jesus Christ!
□老天哪！□
Why the fuck is it so hard to kill one little Chinese girl?
□要殺一個中國小姑娘□ □怎麼他媽的就那麼難！□
You left me for dead... twice.
□你把我扔下等死兩次了□
It will not happen again.
□不會有第三次了□
You come and have a go,if you think you're hard enough.
□如果你覺得自己能耐夠大的話□ □就來試試吧□
- Is that all you got? Huh?
□你就那麼點本事嗎？□
You shoulda stayed in the pits!
□你本應留在山溝裡的□
Less talk, just die.
□少廢話 直接去死□
Talk, talk, talk.
□說 說 說□
No more talk.
□沒機會讓你說了□
- That's enough.
□夠了□
He's dead.
□他已經死了□
Are you sure?
□你確定嗎？□
Thank you.
□謝謝你□
□小嫻□
Xiao Xian.
We were worried sick.
□你還好嗎？□
We came as soon as we got Jaka's phone call.
□我們都擔心死了 剛剛接到□□扎卡先生的電話 馬上就趕過來了□
Jaka?
□扎卡□
I have some good news.
□告訴你一個好消息□
We've arrested the person responsible.
□幕後主使人查到了□
□叫蘇鳳□
□剛剛被逮捕□
She's being extradited to Singapore.
□馬上就會被引渡回新加坡 接受調查□
Stop right there.
You're under arrest. Get up.
I told you... I had a plan.
□我跟你們說了□
□我已經計劃好了□
Good plan. We almost died.
□計劃真不錯 我們差點喪命□
Next time, you get shot.
□下次你來擋子彈□
Bye.
□那再見了□
See you, man.
□再見了□
□ Hey! □
Subtitles by explosiveskull
□ I got that bass gun Bass gun □
□ Everybody jump Got that bass gun, bass gun □
□ Droppin' on that trunk □
□ I got that bass gun Bass gun □
□ Locked and loaded krunk Bass gun, bass gun □
- □ Everybody jump □ - □ Hey! □
□ Hey!
□ Hey! □
- □ Everybody jump □ - □ Hey! □
□ Shake it on the floor Baby, shake it on the floor □
□ Call me crazy kamikaze □
□ When we crash On through that door □
□ Come on □
□ Clap your hands, come on □
□ Feel it hit your chest □
□ Fill your lungs And steal your breath □
□ Got that motion like the oceanSo we floatin' on this mess □
□ Come on □
□ Lift yo hands, come on □
□ I got that bass gun Bass gun □
□ Everybody jump Got that bass gun, bass gun □
□ Droppin' on that trunk □
□ I got that bass gun Bass gun □
□ Locked and loaded krunk Bass gun, bass gun □
- □ Everybody jump □ - □ Hey! □
□ Hey! □
□ Clap your hands Clap your hands □
□ Everybody clap your hands □
□ We came to make some noise □
□ I got my guns You got your toys □
□ Don't try to fight It cant deny it □
□ 'Cause there never was A choice □
□ Come on □
□ Say my name, come on □
□ V-A-N-N-E-S-S □
□ Baby, swing those hips □
□ Like there's venom On those lips □
□ We on that holy spirit Shake, don't spill it □
□ Come on □
□ Baby, baby, come on □
□ I got that bass gun Bass gun □
□ Everybody jump Got that bass gun, bass gun □
□ Droppin' on that trunk □
□ I got that bass gun Bass gun □
□ Locked and loaded krunk Bass gun, bass gun □
- □ Everybody jump □- □ Hey! □
□ Hey! □
- □ Everybody jump □ - □ Hey! □
□ I got that bass gun Bass gun □
□ Everybody jump □
□ Clap your hand Clap your hands □
□ Everybody clap your hands □
□ Clap your hands Clap your hands □
□ Everybody clap your... □
□ Clap your hands □
□ Everybody clap your hands □
□ Clap your hands Clap your hands □
□ I got that bass gun Bass gun □
□ Locked and loaded krunk Bass gun, bass gun □
□ Bass gun □